<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Christian.V</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/</link><description>Recent content on Christian.V</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.118.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:55:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://christianvipp.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creative</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/creative/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:55:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/creative/</guid><description>Recon &amp;amp; Scanning :
Utilizing rustscan and nmap to find open ports.. 2 open ports..
command executed - nmap -sCV -p 22,80 IP -T4 -oG creative
Host: 10.10.37.0 () Status: Up Host: 10.10.37.0 () Ports: 22/open/tcp//ssh//OpenSSH 8.2p1 Ubuntu 4ubuntu0.5 (Ubuntu Linux; protocol 2.0)/, 80/open/tcp//http//nginx 1.18.0 (Ubuntu)/ # Nmap done at Sat Mar 29 22:15:29 2025 -- 1 IP address (1 host up) scanned in 13.10 seconds With nmap, figured out the additional info for the open ports, 22 hosts ssh server and 80 hosts a nginx server with the version information, we could deduce it runs on LINUX host specifically UBuntu.</description></item><item><title>Pyrat</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/pyrat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 06:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/pyrat/</guid><description>recon :
rustscan to find open ports. 2 opened ports..
scanning :
nmap scan to identify services and versions.. ssh and HTTP server running simple http python server..
Enumeration :
Visit the web server running on port 8000
Try fuzzing, nothing
checking with burp, the simple http server version, made some research on it and realized there was a github convo based on it.. saw a poc and tried to recreate it on my own end to understand the attack, seemed like i was confident with that route but did not work.</description></item><item><title>Empire-breakout</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/empire-breakout/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 04:26:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/empire-breakout/</guid><description>Recon :
rust scan
5 open ports..
Scan : Nmap scan
Http server running on apache, Samba server with V. smbd 4.6.2 and another http server hosted by miniserv on V. 1.981 also with 20000 on 1.830
OS runs on debian.
Enumeration :
Website running on port 80 shows default apache page.
viewing it source code beneath shows a message.
Using https:///dcode.fr
Decrypted it to this string..
keep it note, might be useful along the line.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/about/whoami/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/about/whoami/</guid><description>About Me
Hey there! 👋 I’m Christian Victor, a 19-year-old cybersecurity enthusiast from Nigeria, currently living in Łódź, Poland. Right now, I’m officially a management student at AHE University—because who doesn’t need to manage something? But let’s be real, my heart is all about the thrill of cybersecurity.
My Journey Into Hacking
The love for hacking? It started young. I was the kid who set up the family WiFi… and then tried to hack it.</description></item><item><title>Assertion101</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/assertion101/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/assertion101/</guid><description>Recon :
a quick rustscan to find open ports on the target
Scanning :
then a nmap scan for banner grabbing for the open ports
Enumeration :
From the nmap scan, we could deduce that OS runs Linux and specifically.
Nmap scan report for 192.168.170.94 Host is up (0.043s latency). PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.6p1 Ubuntu 4ubuntu0.3 (Ubuntu Linux; protocol 2.0) | ssh-hostkey: | 2048 6e:ce:aa:cc:02:de:a5:a3:58:5d:da:2b:ef:54:07:f9 (RSA) | 256 9d:3f:df:16:7a:e1:59:58:84:4a:e3:29:8f:44:87:8d (ECDSA) |_ 256 87:b5:6f:f8:21:81:d3:3b:43:d0:40:81:c0:e3:69:89 (ED25519) 80/tcp open http Apache httpd 2.</description></item><item><title>Assertion101</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/backup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/backup/</guid><description>Recon :
a quick rustscan to find open ports on the target
![Pasted image 20241024182502.png](/images/Pasted image 20241024182502.png)
Scanning : then a nmap scan for banner grabbing for the open ports
![Pasted image 20241024182934.png](/images/Pasted image 20241024182934.png)
# Nmap 7.94SVN scan initiated Thu Oct 24 18:25:45 2024 as: /usr/lib/nmap/nmap -p 22,80 -sCV -oN assertion.txt 192.168.170.94 Nmap scan report for 192.168.170.94 Host is up (0.043s latency). PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.</description></item><item><title>brute</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/brute/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 21:20:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/brute/</guid><description>Recon : a quick ping to verify the target is up. the target is up, will run a quick rust scan on the target to find open ports.
4 open ports, 21,22,80,3306
will run nmap scan to identify the services and versions running on those ports. the results shows FTP, SSH AND HTTP and MYSQL and their respective versions.
Enumeration:
Started enumeration with the ftp server, will attempt to login with an anonymous user.</description></item><item><title>Shakabrah</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/shakabrah/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 21:09:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/shakabrah/</guid><description>Platform : PG Level : Easy
Reconnaissance :
A simple rustscan to find open ports on target. Scanning :
Then proceeds to scan those ports for running services and version identification using nmap. Enumeration :
Visit the website, it has a functionality to ping ips. i will proceed to ping the localhost what happens is that it tries to make a ping request to the specified ip if correct and the output are the ping responses with 4 counts Foothold :</description></item><item><title>Potato</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/potato/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 21:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/potato/</guid><description>platform : Proving Grounds level : easy
Recon : i will perform a quick rust-scan to see the available open ports. There are three (3) open ports in running on the target, let&amp;rsquo;s enumerate further to understand what services are running on the target ports and their and versions
Scanning &amp;amp; Enumeration : i will also run an nmap scan for further enumeration. The scan result came back and we have ssh , http , ftp running on port 2112, and we can see the ftp server contains some files.</description></item><item><title>Gaara</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/gaara/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 20:40:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/gaara/</guid><description>Platform : Proving Grounds
The target is active and responding to the ICMP ping request.
Recon A quick rust scan to find the open ports on the targets. There are 2 open ports: 22 (SSH) and 80 (HTTP).
Scanning Run an nmap scan to confirm and identify the versions of those services. Yes, SSH and HTTP. Based on the banners (Debian), this is a Linux server.
Enumeration Starting with the web server running on port 80.</description></item><item><title>Blogger</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/blogger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:25:52 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/blogger/</guid><description>Platform: Proving Grounds
Level: Easy
Recon: A rustscan as usual!
Two open ports 22 and 80, by default, we know that is SSH and HTTP.
Scanning: Let&amp;rsquo;s go ahead and scan those ports to know which services run on them and their versions.
SSH and HTTP with their respective versions, and we can deduce the OS is Linux.
Enumeration: I ran a curl command to the webserver, hoping to get some information from the headers.</description></item><item><title>Evil-box</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/evil-box/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:25:52 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/evil-box/</guid><description>Platform : Proving Grounds Level: Easy
Reconnaissance: A rustscan as usual to find open ports, 22 and 80 opened.
Scanning: Performed an nmap scan to find version information on the open ports and operating system identification using the aggressive nmap flag.
An Apache webserver is hosted on port 80, and SSH is running on port 22 as usual.
A quick visit to the website shows a default Apache webserver page.</description></item><item><title>Onsystemshelldredd</title><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/onsystemshelldredd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:25:52 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/onsystemshelldredd/</guid><description>Platform: Proving Grounds Level: Easy
Name: Onsystemshelldredd
Reconnaissance: A quick rustscan shows 2 open ports, 2 and 61000.
Scanning: I performed an nmap scan on the target to identify the services running, but nmap only identified one port (FTP), and not the other.
I ran a separate nmap scan against the port, but nmap didn’t identify the service running on port 61000.
Enumeration: The FTP service on the target had a misconfiguration, allowing anonymous login with a random password.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/dc-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://christianvipp.org/portfolio/dc-4/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>